apartmentcities.com 2017-12-14

# Apartments for Rent - PRIVACY POLICY by ApartmentCities.com

## **Privacy Policy**

ApartmentCities.com respects the privacy of its users. In this document we explain how we use information you supply us via the ApartmentCities.com Web site. 

**Information we Collect**  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like your name and email address), unique identifiers (like your password), and demographic information (like your zip code).  
Certain information, such as passwords and e-mail addresses, is collected in order to, among other things, verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.

**IP Addresses and Cookies**  
We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer our web site, and anonymously track content preferences and traffic patterns. We also use cookies to recognize repeat users, track usage behavior, and facilitate your access to and use of our site. Cookies do not damage files or allow anyone to access your personally identifiable information; they simply allow us to tailor information and advertisements to make your visits more enjoyable and meaningful. They also provide information to us about site usage to help us improve and update our site. We may share aggregate (not individual) site usage statistics and demographic information with advertisers and other third parties, but this information will not include any personally identifiable information.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Disclosure of Information**  
We will never sell or share for consideration any personally identifiable information about you or your business to any third party without first receiving your permission.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at **Apartmentcities.com**
